Scheme of things that are certain plants
which are carnivorous or eating them the
Venus flytrap is one of the best known of
these plants a fly gone to the plant by
a Sweet Sarah Rush is against trigger
Brussel just how these plants digest their
prey has yet to be explained there is much
still to learn about these fascinating
eating plan. This is
a new come through for the left right to
Earth on the meteorite theory five ft
seven.
He was.
Live reports from friends of the world as
witnessing our president and shower of me
chaps there is no record of
a display such as this is going to just
add observatories astronomers are noting
The Fantasticks enough. And are
carefully calculating the effect on
the solar system the consensus of opinion
is that the media rights burn up from the
intense heat that's going
to reach the earth.
I.
Show me here I was on a date
this is a thrilling once in
a lifetime spectacle. A lifetime spectacle
free tickets take any seats now.
I am.
Dr Mike and I take
a look at what's going on. The morning
anyway I'm afraid not Mr Mason. Operations
such as yours it's best to wait the.
Eight o'clock tomorrow morning. And.
Have
a good night. See you in
the morning I hope. Good
night. I'm good for to thank.
Mr Jamieson are you really as
pretty as they say you are.
All morning. Do you really
think I'll be able to sing.
Good night good night.
Bad.
All over the world. Look I
can't leave this specimen at the moment
why don't you go up the tower and have
a look it sounds very spectacular sure
of his own tobacco company probably from
a new way to light up the sky so more
cigarettes where did you hide it this
time it's in the cupboard it's
always in the same company.
I was. I was hoping we could get back
to the district in that sting ray this
evening. There we go again
the subject is. Good with
brilliant marine biologist I'm bored with
Sting Rays I really don't care why sting
ray status but do you care about.
Really what you think. Sooner or later
you're going to have to face the.
Day and night drunk or sober in
the lecture room or a lab or
a deserted lighthouse off the coast
economy down with. Mediocre and all.
I care what happens to us OK I knew
you were
a nice girl at the most oh you talked
yourself into marrying me. All
right. What do you want us to
do I don't know what you want.
But I want to get away from this and
all this pretense of doing important
experiments your idea and then six months
away from the University of time to do
field M.S.G.R.
You let me go back where I can buy
a bottle of Scotch whenever I feel
like I'm up way program to bring me
a single bottle every seven days
what about the equipment needed
to about the fish. In the seat I.
Will leave the island tomorrow.
I. Don't.
Know. Why.
I'm.
Going. To
Google
or Giga.
Room.
Eight now. You know.
Miss Davis and.
Hello hello. Hello.
Mistakes than.
Mistake. That anybody.
Doctor's office building I'm sorry I just
couldn't wait to get those bandages off
you can see mace there but I can't
believe what I see what's happened
to please take me to my office.
I tried the other side to certain
the beams on the few Yes I'm
alright that's enough
is the blinds drawn and
yes it would be kind enough to put it up.
For the doctor sums what's happened they
optic nerves are gone the glare of the
meteorites last night will probably one
of the few people left in London who can
still see this morning mist I don't envy
on. I don't think I'd care to see the
zings doing like you'd see in the
outer office in my desk you'll find
a black leather kids would
be good enough to get
a film and of course. That's
not bad.
Oh it is.
No sign of the book no sign of anything
should be here hours ago. There's nothing
on the menu I've been enjoying.
Suppose you're losing valuable
drinking time. I'm sorry
to look out repeat the entire population
of England appears to be afflicted with
blindness as
a result of watching the meteorite shot
last night this is the Royal Dockyard at
Devonport a number of naval personnel
have escaped like we are trying to set up
a rescue center all those who are still
able to see I urged to make their way to
the dockyard urgent warning all of
England appears to be infected with
a strange new plot that can inflict
a fatal sting. It is also rumored
that this plant and I proved itself
a move or bust if you are blind
stay indoors if you can see keep
a constant lookout we will return to the
air with further bullets and stay tuned to
this wavelength.
When we go.
Up
to.
The thing.
We. Please remain. Do not.
The only danger is that you will injure
yourself accidentally stopped by. Smoke.
Like mad. They fear of all electrical
equipment we are doing everything
possible to get help we are any trains
running I don't know suddenly it went dark
and I can see can you help me sir please
can you help me with that problem can you
help me I couldn't help overhearing
the attacks if you could just make
a telephone call for me.
I'm sorry I'm no taxis
on the phones don't work. The
air
going to
go
eat
thank you I
am
you. You are and
you look you
my thank
you I am what I say what I
am speaking only yes.
Come on the
outside
OK THANK YOU THANK YOU
OUT think
you are and.
Were in that plane I'll be
a self I was in the market for oh I didn't
know I ran away from that if you think
boarding school or your parents I haven't
come and cut anything thank you no one
can take care of me. Thank you close.
Always find out.
Mom let's get out of my ship.
And.
Live.
Right here.
Other than.
That See if you can find
some rocks come on.
He.
Felt.
Good. Good.
Good.
Thank you. I can understand French
I can come up with the saying.
Oh thank you thank you oh so this is
talk to me well continue sounding as
well as he can something you know.
You. Have to go.
Come. Calling me
a day later if you read
me come in please S. S.
Mith and calling May Day.
The company yes but doesn't
the passengers have started to panic
so I'm going to go to the doctor but.
This is the captain speaking Attention All
Passengers that is now on board who can
help you where right hearing for
a rescue vessel the only immediate danger
is that you may injure yourself by moving
around everyone right where you off and
if that is anyone who can see even
a child plays come up on the bridge.
I can think of it but you know I couldn't
put it that much you don't do this as
some of us. Don't seem like you have.
Buddy buddy to really go but I'm also clear
on where you were please don't throw
five pounds he says because you need to do
to. Him what you. Know how will you know
you should do this on the body the body
feels the others who can see what he does
make contact right three
five feet from Cory.
He. Please don't go down
though can you read me
tell you really made
a baby girl please come and
please pull down and please
pull and. Still revive it
trying.
Hard revives think it was just about
gone so how much longer and even though.
The. Friend you read.
Can be very very very.
Very good because I'm just current again
so it won't last much longer they want to
know what's. Going to tell them something.
Tell them tell them everything's all
right not to want to go into foster the
sense of votes that were coming into that.
Yes then.
Ladies and gentlemen please don't think
about as we are up to that I'm sure you
know everything from I think you
know. Possible say that species.
Causes it that's NEWSNIGHT.
And that's all right
Private see blind to all and I don't
see these thousand dollars Oh
and please oh
yes. Oh yes I am.
Good.
Thing you.
Tell us one of those plants growing up
there where it's alleged by the come.
To.
This.
One coming. Keep you know there's
no sense in getting killed by
a plant. Who didn't care what happened to
me I don't see much President today but.
It was here. I know it was he.
Thought that's get back inside.
Place.
To slow play local
players. Who
claim.
Claim. I'm going
to go
play
. A little player.
Playing
player. Are going.
To look. At me I'm
a donut. Hole Oh.
Do you think that. Because of one word just
for some it is impossible for delegates
to get
a very sweet scent with millions of this
in evidence has become dangerous this will
be I'm not going there is no one here
who can see there is no one left.
Leg. There's nothing there.
For.
Will not stop and. Let
me see that map again.
Thank goodness the coca.
But nothing because
you can see. Well give
me here. Just the way.
Mr Wrenn back at the coke at this is
Mr Mason and Susan I don't know if.
You found some miss coca This is Mr Mason
and Susan I do Muskoka they can see. I
do focus and focus.
On the Blind people do you have it about
her. But you must be very hungry.
My sister and I would try to improve we
collided with Mr Ransom both our cars were
really no one was badly hurt but through
it all three under sedation let's not
thanks to Mr rent the shelter
became a hospital yes
a tragic irony sicced did well
on the healthy become. Your
daughter's Spears. Come along my dear.
Good night happy. How is your
daughter and me I am certain
is not my daughter where you found each
other in London and since then we've sort
of been stuck with each other.
It's nothing to be
afraid of I don't fancy.
The team. Which didn't suit us she's an
English girl and has just arrived and those
who say. I brought it to you Bettina because
she still feels strange here and you
speaking. By day to me talking.
But you can see how can
you. Think I can tell
a good many things I think is the right
people react when you talked. To I can get
anything like that here can you
tell who. That being. But you have
a very grown up twelve
and I think you are.
Coming down right right and.
That's right. You've got
a good sense of humor too I can tell you
because you couldn't I just love climbs on
them up. To get something to.
Until things get back to normal you know
when it comes to stay here and how it was
the past few days I've seen London us
a lot in between things are never going
back to normal so I've tried to impress on
my story that I have a face to.
Face is fine Mr Right but we need
a lot more than ever going to survive why
shouldn't we so well in France alone as
over fifty million people almost every one
of them blind is going to be starvation
five just once anyone caught
in the middle doesn't stand
a chance I think we ought to get out of
here go on to Spain how can you know it's
an event I don't and even still how
could we get all the people that
we could miss to miss in your
chest when you read. What Mr and
I told you with things like if you sit
there with your eyes closed let this thing
on over here you're the one who's running
away perhaps you'll change your mind I
hope you and Susan will decide to
stay and help us connect tonight.
A warm generous hearted woman
but I'm afraid but he stopped.
With.
The lights on the game yes they got the
electricity going candlelight Oh yes we've
been good friends he's back to normal maybe
I can reach him one on. The lights on
Yes Isn't it wonderful. I know.
I'm all right you're going
to answer with around. Why are you so sure
I want to put some fuel in me on Julie
more of the generator as well as that last
will have light that I don't know about
the phone.
Cords of the RIP system it's good to see
you looking you can I assure you it's not
for the greater glory of science I just
want us to survive we've. Done it all I'm
not even a botanist Is it
a plant or an animal or north doesn't
seem to have any central nervous system
no circulation then how does it move all
plans small. And they don't usually pull
themselves out of the ground and chase
you. We could find out how this thing
functions we like figure out
an easier way of killing it.
You must get some sleep.
It's not time just an hour.
Then
a week I promise. You
a. Time.
You really must get some sleep.
It's. Kind of.
It got out it came to life and it got our.
Like and it looks like Wells couple of up
and you can kill them as well telling how
many of them are up against
a hammer and nails. It's
like being nailed in your coffee.
If you're doing God if I wanted to
talk to you Mr mess if you should
be wondering Rob yourself but I had to
talk to you just for that if is it true
you're going to leave
us. To get this thing.
Yes but what about the rest of us Dana the
only way I can help is to try to find
some real health I can't do it by
staying here are you coming back to us
yes if I can. If you do come back
mom I better get you back inside.
It's.
A little.
Interested to know what
a profit the original Triffitt the con are
Shawna greenhouse several years ago was
known to come to earth and to me try this
reappearance must have been caused by the
meteorite explosion of the other not why
should they attack people most plants
thrive on animal waste but I'm afraid this
mutation possesses an appetite for the
animal itself which must be how
they propagate. Millions of them one
night when the night everybody.
So that was Mr Right. Later to Mr
Right even to sixty six down. Look Mr
Right Now whether you like it or not
we're going to have to pack up and leave
do you bring so much to cause. You tell
them Mr Goldberg Mason is quite right Mr
Rath in the next twenty four hours the
vicinity be swarming the truth that I
cannot keep all these people here to die I
grew up with them they're my
friends don't you understand this.
I don't expect. That's
what I want to tell you.
The mom told her.
You say something about too
long the naval base being
a rescue center along. Course the French
base in the Mediterranean there Marseilles
Yes. He did.
Listen. To this all right.
It's my bank account for the blood. Of.
Baba. Yaga.
Let's listen let's while. Some may
come fix I think they take. And
make him dance with him. They've also
kinds of food I wish people would know I
don't know but it's not and they can
see yes Mr if he's not with them. But
they said they can anyone who.
I. I.
I.
Would. Stay here and lock all
the doors they don't want me.
I. I.
I. Love them
I. Love them I.
Don't know what up.
Lucky. You're
a better side. Unlike
. The thing I said to you back to the
ship door. I had no right to say.
Makes you feel any better I probably
would have said the same thing under the
circumstances. Feel guilty. Maybe.
You know my. Mind. Because you
survived Katrina Coburn all rest
dead. When you're alive and you wonder
why I. Had said that can I know the
feeling. When the war
you get a sure shot up
a minute into. All your friends gone
nowhere Hampel left ask yourself why me
wanna someone better.
Well we're going to Spain. I was
a big American naval base in southern
Spain I could be. A copper disaster I got
supplies a discipline. So we had
a friendship too real. Negative
. My present need to
consider solution negative
Not that I expected a little
I didn't think we'd find
a magic bullet but look absolutely nothing
seems to affect the station. He lives
they grow they take nourishment.
They have sensory response. From
soap and expend energy. No matter what
they're made of the must be something that
will interrupt their life cycle fundamentally
it's a simple problem like finding
a week to. Go help out there.
Being nothing in the air for days can't
help thinking about that last radio call
from. The way the place caught fire and
blew up like that it was just like you
singing to the end of the world but it's
not the end of the world not quite yet
there's nothing here in
front of us that has to be.
If we're going to find the one some We'd
better find it pretty soon what are they
doing up. Stealing
images like gods outside
a condemned cell Oh let's get
through this checklist again.
Oh oh.
You're
a good cause you must be town I'm
going to buy you some rest. Now
don't look. All right but don't want to
rock that we can find something over need
right away from.
Me I'm sorry you are burning. Nothing.
You. Do you think we have
a chance. And should taste this coffee of
mine you know nothing more is going to
happen. You know coffee very good
in fact your hand man in the kitchen.
Been doing for myself the longer
you have never been married so why does the
number than one spot long enough to get
caught and now you are saddled with
a family that might have its point. We
could do that we'll take it. Because well
we did in the field somewhere anyway up
on the podium we find. Now so isn't the
reason but we kept thinking whether.
He's not being exposed. He's only doing
what's right for all of those you never
hurt you know if you can you know that.
I took the cookie I think so.
When we find out.
How many body here.
Please please come in come
in oh I got to ask how.
It is man but I gotta hand it why didn't
it all figured out I knew it that's my
rope. We still have a go I'm
going to miss THIS IS SO is
a mystery. But piece.
That I stuff three guests
this is my wife Doris. Well. Now we know
that we are not the only two people left
in this part of the world I
believe that someone with an I.Q.
Of about why I put up there ARE
YOU think we are expecting
a baby and we need someone who can
help perhaps the two ladies who.
You can't see both seemed so natural My
wife has been blind for many years now
she's teaching me how to get on. But
you ladies will stay and help because.
P P fifty dollars if
you. Would have come in.
We were trying to get to be but you don't
know about that. They had to evacuate the
naval base. By submarine
I heard it on my radio
some submarines that were submerged during
the night of the meteorites that entire
crews would all right I tried to contact
them with my designs Mr Bob Something went
wrong I can neither transmit
nor is he. Going to take
a look at it maybe I can fix it or are you
familiar. With the first mate I have to
have
a working knowledge of and. From
the Gibraltar rescue center final survivor
pick up will be on Saturday at L.A.
County. We repeat our warning brass bands
of traffic the roaming the area do
not travel at night barricade all
doors we repeat our warning do not
travel at night barricade
all doors final survive
a pickup will be on Saturday at the L.A.
County and that's tomorrow. Well you
the first thing in the morning.
Oh I tell you what that's what.
Probably pretty doggone.
Well it works. Hard you don't know.
Baby Boy Yes. I was. But I'm
a mother she's weak
supposed to be expected.
That Susan.
Look live. In go one on the
switch.
Live.
At least. Six
lives
leave me. Subsets.
Let's limit.
I.
Live.
To see it live don't have enough power. To
say. Listen.
Listen listen.
listen Listen listen
.
You know didn't want to.
Let.
Thank you keep coming I don't know
Susan and I must be some reason.
Maybe that's it. Maybe
a sound that attracts them. Generator. I'm
going to. Write it down to
the tracks.
Lead them to it. Give me them away to.
The Pied Piper. To show
you. How when I'm gone
obligates they got but until then
dull noise that oh all right come on.
What about you. I see you now driving.
When there's
a. You're
.
The girl.
The
in
the
small and
pearl the in.
The
early.
M.
. One
I'm going to bore Mr Press play.
When I'm writing the part in five minutes.
You're. Married.
Or way.
Or are.
Rare.
This is
a Dobro to rescue center for the Mediterranean
area because what I can see has been
made on schedule this is the final rescue
operation for the present stay tuned to
this wavelength for the Bulletin repeat
stay tuned to this wavelength for further
Bulletin. To produce when
Let's get back to work.
Is away from my windows
file staring at them.
I'm sorry I'm sorry.
The.
People.
Live.
Live
live.
Live live.
Live.
Live
. Live says.
Do you want to.
I am.
See what. Two thirds of the
office covered with it.
Until you such and all the while
the answer is like something.
Else simple methods have been found to
destroy the ship. Sea water from which life
on earth had sprung became the means of
preserving life on Earth. Mankind survived
and once again had reason to give thanks
Lynn.
Lynn
.